americanabest.com 2009-06-29

# americanabest.com

## Privacy Policy 

The user's personal data shall be used by americanabest.com in compliance with the principles of privacy protection set forth in Legislative Decree no. 196 of 30 June 2003 and in other applicable regulations. This information statement pertains to the personal data sent by the user at the time of registration, as well as to those generated from the user’s visits to and surfing on our website.

americanabest.com. subjects the personal data of users to all the processing operations contemplated in Legislative Decree no. 196/2003 – that is to say, data collection, storage, organisation, conservation, processing, changes, selection, extraction, comparison, use, interconnection and any and all operations useful to the supply of the services requested, including the communication of such data to third parties where necessary – mainly using automated and computerised procedures. Such data may also be organised in databanks or archives. In particular, the goals of the processing of personal data are as follows:

a) the supply of the service;  
b) the supply of information and/or the sending of notices pertaining to the service;  
c) participation in competition for a price eventually connected to the service;  
d) compliance with any and all accounting and tax requirements;  
e) tracing alleged offenders only where specifically required to do so and only on behalf of the competent authorities.  
In the case where the user has provided his/her consent to such effect:  
f) the supply of information and/or offers of services that americanabest.com and/or its associated and/or subsidiary undertakings, as well as its trade partners and outsourcers, may feel will be of interest for the user, without such use entailing the transfer of personal data to third parties. americanabest.com. undertakes never to transfer the data of its customers to third parties;  
g) checking the quality of the services offered;  
h) sending notices and advertising information pertaining to its own as well as third parties’ products and initiatives;  
i) undertaking market and statistical research, marketing initiatives and tracking product preferences.

The Customer may access his or her data at any time and exercise the rights mentioned in article 7 of Legislative Decree no. 196/2003.

Personal data are divided into two categories: compulsory and optional, as indicated in the registration procedure.

The supply of compulsory data and the processing thereof for the abovementioned purposes are strictly functional for the performance of the indicated service. Any refusal by the user to provide such data or any refusal to provide consent for the processing thereof shall make it impossible for the user to access the service offered by americanabest.com. The other data collected are requested so as to help americanabest.com. constantly improve its service. The Customer is free to provide or withhold such data.

americanabest.com. informs its users that, pursuant to art. 7 of Legislative Decree no. 196/2003, all users are entitled:  
a) to be informed of the existence of any data processing which may relate to them;  
b) to be informed of the details of the controller and the processor;  
c) to obtain from the controller: confirmation as to the existence of personal data, the communication thereof and of their origin, as well as the logic and purposes upon which the processing is based;  
d) the cancellation, transformation into anonymous form or the blocking of the data processed in breach of law;  
e) the updating, rectification and integration of the data;  
f) attestation that the operations referred to in the previous point have been disclosed to those persons to whom the data have been communicated and/or distributed;  
g) to oppose, in whole or in part, for legitimate reasons, the processing of their personal data;  
h) to modify their consent, even later withdrawing the same, in whole or in part, with regard to the processing of their personal data for the purposes of commercial information or for the carrying out of market research or commercial communications and the like. The personal data acquired by americanabest.com. may be communicated to all employees, collaborators and consultants under any entitlement whatsoever by our Company, and to all the corporate organs. The same data may, moreover, be communicated a) to companies that are associated or affiliated or forming part of the "americanabest.com" or to the commercial partners of americanabest.com. (manufacturers, suppliers, carriers etc.) or to the companies which perform surveys on customer preferences, always in respect of the purposes of the handling indicated above
